http://www.alumni.berkeley.edu/privacy-policy

Skip to content
CommunityCommunity ProgramsGet InvolvedBerkeley ChangemakerAlumni ChaptersAdvocacyThe Berkeley NetworkMore ProgramsDistinguished Cal AlumniAlumni Scholars ProgramStudent ProgramsAchievement AwardsVolunteer AwardsMore
Shop CAA
More
A Message from Our Executive Director: Let There Be Light
EventsEvergreen EventsEvent CalendarCampus EventsAthleticsHost Your Event at Alumni HouseUpcoming EventsBerkeley Network WebinarsCareer ConnectionsStudent EventsVirtual ProgramsWho Are We Now?More
Events Calendar
More
Who Are We Now?: A Conversation with Cal Student-Athletes
MembershipAbout CAA MembershipMembership RatesMember BenefitsReasons to Join CAAMembership MattersUC Library AccessUC Extension DiscountMembership DetailsJoin NowRenew Your MembershipUpdate Your Contact InfoMembership FAQSave at the Cal Student StoreAlumni Insurance PlansMore
Become a Golden Bears Life Member
More
New Grads Save on CAA Membership
VolunteerVolunteer OpportunitiesScholarship SelectionBecome a District ChairStart an Alumni ChapterJoin an Alumni ChapterMore OpportunitiesThe Berkeley NetworkVolunteer Interest FormWhy Volunteer with CAAMore
Become a Volunteer
More
Read Scholarship Applications
GiveDonateWhy Give to CAAHow to GiveThe CAA Fund SocietyGiving NotesMore Ways to GiveThe CAA FundGive to ScholarshipsTelephilanthropyContact the Development TeamMore
Support CAA’s future.
More
How to Give
TravelCal Discoveries TravelNorth AmericaEuropeOceaniaCentral and South AmericaAfricaAll ToursSpring 2021Summer 2021Fall 2021Winter 2021-2022Tour LecturersMore
Cal Discoveries Travel COVID-19 Update
More
Taste of Sicily: Wine Tasting with Cal Discoveries Travel
Camp at the LairOur VacationsFamily CampSpecialty CampsCollege Prep CampLair WeddingsGroup Rentals & RetreatYour VacationBook A TentCalendarRatesAccommodationsFor Your StayLair FAQMore
Get on Our Mailing List
More
Opening safely in 2021
California MagazineMagazine TopicsArts + LettersCal CultureHuman BehaviorInnovationLaw + PolicyScience + HealthCalifornia OnlineJust InIssue ArchiveAdvertise With UsSubmission GuidelinesClass NotesAbout California MagazineMore
150 Years of Women at UC Berkeley
More
Latest Issue: Fall 2020
The Cal Alumni Association (CAA) is sensitive to your concerns about privacy, and places your concerns as a priority. We are committed to preserving the privacy of any personal information that you choose to give us through the CAA website. Such information may be requested when you purchase membership, tickets to an event, or register for any number of other services that CAA may provide.
Any reference to “CAA”, “we,” “our,” or “us” in this policy refers to the Cal Alumni Association.
CAA will:
Provide to anyone, upon request, notice of their ability to opt out of information exchanges.
Honor customer opt-out requests not to have their contact information transferred to third parties for marketing purposes.
Accept and maintain requests to stop receiving communication or other solicitations from CAA.
Collection of Information
We assure you that all purchases made on the CAA website are secure and utilize advanced encryption technology. Your data is carefully protected from loss, misuse, disclosure, and unauthorized access. Any personal data collected is used solely for the purpose of helping us to better serve you.
Information CAA Collects about You
Contact information: CAA collects information about you when you subscribe to a newsletter, provide contact information through one of our webforms, or register for an event.
Content provided through our websites: CAA collects information you provide to us through our websites, such as surveys, social media posts, quizzes, and other interactive features.
Payment information: CAA collects certain payment and billing information from you when you purchase a membership through our website. All payment details are collected through secure payment processing services.
In order to provide CAA members with valuable services and membership benefits, CAA maintains business relationships with a small number of carefully selected and screened third-party organizations. From time to time, CAA may share personal information (such as name and address) to our business partners in order to offer CAA members desirable products, discounts, and services. You have the right to control whether you receive product or service information from our affinity partners, including by opting out of affinity partner mailings.
Cookies and Analytics Partners
About Cookies
This website uses cookies for session maintenance: they allow us to see which pages a user has visited, but do not carry any identifying information about the user.
Google Analytics
CAA’s website uses Google Analytics advertising and reporting features to collect user demographics and interests reports to better understand its visitors. CAA allows Google Analytics to collect data about CAA’s website traffic via cookies and anonymous identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. You can opt out of this Google Analytics data collection feature at any time by visiting Google Analytics Opt-Out. Learn more about how Google uses information from sites that use Google Analytics.
Facebook
CAA’s website uses cookies to measure traffic from the content and advertisements CAA displays on Facebook. You can learn more about Facebook’s cookies and Data Policy, as well as how to control what data Facebook uses about you, by visiting Facebook Cookies & Other Storage Technologies.
External Websites
The CAA website contains links to other websites that are operated and maintained by third parties and are not under the control or supervision of CAA. CAA does not control any material on linked sites, and this privacy policy will not apply to other websites. Such linked sites should be accessed at the user’s discretion. We recommend that you read the privacy policy of any linked site before disclosing your personal information.
Policy Updates
CAA reserves the right to change this agreement and to make changes to any of the products or programs described in the site at any time without notice or liability. Any such revisions are prospectively binding on you, and therefore, please be sure to periodically visit this page when you use the site to review the current agreement that binds you.
Inquiries
Contact CAA Web Communications.
CAA’s Privacy Policy was last revised July 6, 2018.
blue-and-gold
